## Wong Yao Zu Donavon

donwong2308.github.io • donavon wong@yahoo.com.sg • 97212308

## **ABOUT ME**

Currently pursuing a diploma for Infocomm & Security in Nanyang Polytechnic. I am constantly striving for excellence in any tasks I do. My strong sense of responsibility and time management allows me to handle multiple projects at once and complete it well. From my past experiences, I have gained leadership skills enabling me to lead and co-ordinate my team to handle group assignments beyond the expectations set for us. Other than programming and studying, I also do a fair share of sports to balance my lifestyle out.

## **EDUCATION**

Nanyang Polytechnic - Infocomm & Security

Year 1 Sem 1 Director's List

• Year 1 Sem 2 Director's List

National Junior College- GCE 'A' Levels

Integrated Programme (IP) at National Junior College

PSLE

Jan 2015 – Dec 2016

Jan 2011 – Dec 2014

Jan 2005 – Dec 2010

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Past Employer Feb 2017 – Apr 2017

The Fun Empire-Organizers of fun team building games

#### **Part-Time Basic Facilitator**

- Help to interact with the clients and facilitate the team bonding event by explaining the gameplay and advice on strategies of the game.
- Clients have provided feedback that the facilitators have immensely helped made the event more enjoyable by creating a fun and enthusiastic atmosphere for the clients.

Past Employer Jun 2019 – Aug 2019

Climb Asia

## **Part-Time Retail Assistant**

- Assist in manning of the shop and the necessary shop operations such as ensuring the shop is nice and tidy, packing
  of the stocks in the store room, etc
- Interact with customers and help them make wise decisions and provide professional advice on the climbing equipment they should purchase.
- Do cashiering duties.
- Operation of scissors lift to obtain stocks from the warehouse and ensure there are enough stocks in the main shop.

Past Employer Aug 2019 – Sep 2019

DKSH

#### **Warehouse Assistant**

- Assist in sorting of healthcare products
- Assist in stock counting.
- Assist in picking and packing in the Cold Room.
- Assist in arranging stocks by pallets and shifting pallets using a pallet jack.

Past Employer Jan 2020

LF Logistics

## **Warehouse Assistant**

- Assist in sorting of nutrition products
- Assist in stock counting.
- Assist in picking and packing.
- Assist in arranging stocks by pallets and shifting pallets using a pallet jack.

Apr 2019 - Present

Past Employer Nov 2019, Feb 2020

5 Hour Energy

#### Promoter

- Assist in manning of the booth and helping customers redeem their receipts for a lucky draw.
- Interact with customers and give them free samples to try and explain the product to them.
- Interact with kids and help them play a vending machine game to win prizes.

Past Employer Mar 2020

Health Promotion Board

## **IQUIT Ambassador**

- Rove around public places with an Adwalker to interact with smokers to persuade them to participate in the IQUIT Campaign.
- Conduct Smokalyzer tests on smokers to alert them on the damage smoking does to their lungs.

Current Employer Mar 2020 - Present

The Lab Education

#### **Assistant Instructor**

• Assist the Main Instructor in guiding students aged 11 and 12 to build and code robots using Lego Mindstorm.

#### **Main Instructor**

• Teach children the logic of coding using block coding and implement it in Lego Mindstorm robots.

Current Internship Jun 2020 - Present

Centre for Strategic Infocomm Technologies

#### Intern

• Assist in the development of security features for government websites, eg: prevent SQL injections, DDOS attacks, etc.

## **CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

# NYP Bouldering Team 2020 - 2021 Captain

- Responsible for the team's attendance and discipline
- In charge of organizing trainings
- · Assist in the administrative procedures of the team, eg: details for competitions such as POL-ITE

Represented NYP in POL-ITE

Represented NYP in Gravical 2020

NJC Climbing 2015 - 2016

## Vice-Captain

- Responsible for the team's attendance and discipline
- In charge of the team's monetary funds
- Assist in the administrative procedures of the team, eg: details for competitions/overseas trip to Malaysia.
- Represented NJC in various competitions: NSBC, NSCC, Gravical, Pumpfest, BoulderActive, etc.

Canoeing 2011 – 2014

## **Land Training IC**

- Oversee the team's physical fitness and organize training sessions to maintain the fitness level of the team.
- Represented NJC in various Inter-School competitions
- Attained School Colors Award
   2013

# COMMUNITY SERVICE PROGRAMMES/ LEADERSHIP ROLES/ INTERESTS/ OTHERS

•	Razer Hackathon Participant	2020
•	NYP Vietnam Industry Overseas Trip	2019
•	AWS Cloud Services Workshop	2019
•	Certified Ethical Hacking v9 Certification	2017
•	VIA Advocate	2016
•	Climbing Level 2 Certification	2016
•	Orientation Group Leader (OGL)	2015, 2016
•	Participant of Social Enterprise Challenge	2015
•	Maldives Overseas Value-In-Action (OVIA)	2015
•	Leader in boarding (LIB)	2015
•	Volunteer at Silver Fiesta organized by YMCA	2014
•	ABRSM Grade 6 Violin	2012